* Shop

JoinLog in

Introducing the Privacy Statement

What data we collect and why

Where do we obtain your data

Why we collect your data

How we disclose your data

How we protect your data

How long we store your personal information

How we use cookies and similar technologies

Your choices for managing your data

Notice of Financial Incentive

Minors

How to contact us

PayPal Honey Privacy Statement
------------------------------

### Last updated September 23, 2024

Introducing the Privacy Statement

This privacy statement (“Privacy Statement”) explains how PayPal, Inc. (“PayPal Honey” or “we”) collects and processes information from members and users of the website, software applications, and other online services we provide (collectively “PayPal Honey's products”). PayPal Honey's products include, but are not limited to, the PayPal Honey extension for web browsers (the “Extension”), the PayPal Honey mobile application (the “Mobile App”), and the website located at www.joinhoney.com (the “Website”), collectively, (the “Services”).  
  
To the extent that PayPal Honey has links to other websites (like retailers), please note that we do not own, operate, or control them, and they have their own controlling privacy policies that you should review.

What data we collect and why

_Personal Identifiers._  
  
In order to provide our Services, PayPal Honey collects information that you share directly with us when you use the Services.  
  
During the registration process we may collect your name, email address, IP address, your device's unique ID (where available), member password and other registration information. When you sign up with your existing PayPal account, PayPal Honey sees basic profile information you provided to PayPal, like your name, email address and country location. We may also collect information needed to complete your purchases, such as your billing address.  
  
We may also collect any other information you provide when you communicate with PayPal Honey through email or other means.  
  
If you choose to link a social media profile (like Facebook) at sign-in, PayPal Honey will store this information for login purposes. Linking your social media profile grants PayPal Honey access to the profile, but only to the extent allowed by your permission settings, that social media platform's terms of service, and this Privacy Statement. We do not track your social media activity or post anything on your behalf.  
  
_PayPal Honey Payment Information._  
  
We may collect your payment information when you purchase gift cards or other products or services from PayPal Honey. We also save your payment information to your PayPal Honey account in order to allow you to check out easier when shopping on retailers' websites. In those cases, you will be asked to input a payment option (i.e., a debit or credit card), as well as information needed to complete those purchases (such as your billing address). In those instances, your payment information is securely stored with our payment processor, Braintree (a PayPal service). Alternatively, if you purchase an item on a third-party merchant's website displayed within the PayPal Honey Mobile App, that merchant (not PayPal Honey) will collect, store, and process your payment information in connection with that purchase.  
  
_Commercial Information._  
  
We collect information about your purchases on retail sites when using PayPal Honey as well as shopping activity and goods or services considered on our merchants, partners, sites or businesses that our users transact with for the purpose of obtaining goods or services (“Partners and Merchants”).  
  
_Internet or Network Activity._  
  
We collect this information to provide PayPal Honey members with a better way to shop online and to help us develop, improve, and market our Services. This may include data such as:

* the type of device you're using
* operating system
* browser type
* event stamp
* error logs
* information about the retail site that lets us know which coupons and promos to find for you
* information about pricing and availability of items
* name of the retailer
* page views

To understand how you engage with our Services, we use common digital tools that allow us to see if you opened an email we sent, visited a link in those emails, or generally interacted with PayPal Honey as a result of our marketing efforts.

_Shopping and Usage Data._  
  
On retail sites, PayPal Honey collects the name of the retailer, page views, and in some cases, product information that allows us to track price changes and update our product catalog. We may also collect information regarding your purchases on a retail site while using PayPal Honey (for example, the transaction value, and the fact that an order was completed or returned) for purposes including internal analytics, commission collection, and managing Rewards. The information enables us to improve our products and gives us insights about coupons, deals, pricing, and availability of retail items, which we can offer to the rest of the PayPal Honey community. We may also use this information to understand your shopping history, merchant and shopping preferences to provide you with a more tailored, relevant experience or show sponsored product offers that may interest you when you use the Services or you use the PayPal or Venmo services.  
  
When you are on a retailer's site that offers the Services, PayPal Honey will collect information about that site that lets us know which coupons and promos to find for you.  
  
As you use our Services, we might also collect data, such as:

* items you save in order to monitor price drops (Droplist)
* coupons, promo codes, and deals you found
* friend referrals from your contacts to PayPal Honey
* stores you “follow”

_Inference Data._  
  
We may infer information about you such as your preferences and shopping behavior, based on your interactions with our Services or with our Partners and Merchants.  
  
_Sensitive Personal Data._  
  
We may disclose your sensitive personal information as appropriate to carry out legitimate business activities allowed by law, but we do not sell or share your sensitive personal data.  
  
_Aggregate and Anonymized Data._  
  
We may also use the information we collect in aggregate or otherwise anonymized form. This lets us look at interactions with our site and products generally and does not identify you or any specific person. We use this general data for research, development, marketing, analytics, and to enhance the shopping experience for the Honey community.

Where do we obtain your data

We may obtain the above categories of personal information from the following different sources:

* from you, including from your interactions with us and use of the Service, as well as when you use the PayPal or Venmo services
* Third parties, including Service Providers, Retailers, and Operating Systems
* Connected Accounts: accounts you agree to link to PayPal Honey, such as social network accounts.

Why we collect your data

In addition to the uses described above, we also collect your information for a variety of reasons, including to provide our Services as well as for the following reasons:

* To provide our Services: such as to setup your account, to create an inventory of functioning coupons, deals, pricing and availability of retail items, to track price changes, update our product catalog, commission collection, create Droplists, and managing Rewards.
* To manage and improve our Services: to make sure our products our working correctly, conduct internal analytics.
* To manage fraud and risk.
* To personalize your shopping experiences, including when you use the Service or you use the PayPal or Venmo services: to provide you with a more tailored, relevant experience or show sponsored product offers that may interest you, see a personalized recommendation feed.
* Associate information about you: If you use Venmo or PayPal, we may associate information about your transactions and experiences using those Services to personalize content and offers and improve your use of the PayPal Honey services.
* To market our Services, including when we associate information about you.
* To communicate with you.
* To comply with Laws: to comply with applicable laws and rules and enforce our agreements with you and other people who use our Services.
* To process information about your contacts: with your consent, we may collect your friends’ contact information for referrals.

How we disclose your data

We do not sell personal information to third parties for money or share your personal information for cross context behavioral advertising, including sensitive personal information, for cross context behavioral advertising. We may disclose your sensitive personal information as appropriate to carry out legitimate business activities allowed by law.  
  
In addition, we may disclose your personal information with your consent or in ways you'd expect (as we explain here).  
  
We may disclose information with the following categories of third parties:

* With our service providers (businesses that work for and with us) for the purpose of running PayPal Honey and fulfilling our commitments to you. These include businesses that perform services on our behalf, including to help us maintain our products, manage coupons codes and offers, to provide support for legal, banking, security protection, payment processing, our own marketing, and customer service. Please know that when we disclose information with our service providers, it's for the purposes outlined in this Privacy Statement and not for their independent use. The personal information we disclose may include your identification information, your shopping and usage data, internet or network activity, commercial information, inferences, and sensitive personal information.
* With PayPal Companies, to manage Rewards and personalize your use of the Services and your use of the PayPal or Venmo services. The personal information we disclose may include your identification information, your shopping and usage data, and commercial information.
* With your consent, to Partners and Merchants that you and we interact with, to help ourselves and our Partners and Merchants personalize services when you shop with PayPal so you can have a better and more relevant experience. Personal Information we disclose includes, for example, products, brands, sizes, preferences and styles we think you’ll like.
    * If you decide that you prefer to no longer participate in sharing for the personalized PayPal offers, you may change your preferences in your account settings. If you opt-out, we will continue to disclose your personal information necessary to complete transactions you initiate, but will not disclose personal information to Partners and Merchant for personalized experiences when you pay with PayPal.
* With authorities, as required by law, or to comply with or respond to a valid government request; or when we believe in good faith that it's necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, or investigate fraud. The personal information we disclose may include your identification information, your shopping and usage data, internet or network activity, commercial information and sensitive personal information.
* With a buyer or successor if PayPal, Inc. is involved in a merger, acquisition, or similar corporate transaction. If that happens, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on the Website of any change in ownership, as well as any choices you will have as a result. The personal information we disclose may include your identification information, your shopping and usage data.

How we protect your data

The security of your information is important to us. We have a team dedicated to protecting your information and have put in place physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards.  
  
These measures include limiting access, using encryption, testing for vulnerabilities, advanced malware detection, employing pseudonymization and anonymization techniques, and more.  
  
Despite our efforts, we can't guarantee that user information will not be accessed, viewed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed as a result of a breach of any of our safeguards. You provide us with information at your own risk.

How long we store your personal information

We retain personal information for as long as needed or permitted in context of the purpose for which it was collected and consistent with applicable law.  
  
The criteria used to determine our retention period is as follows:

* Personal information used for the ongoing relationship between you and PayPal Honey is stored for the duration of the relationship plus a period of 10 years, unless we need to keep it longer, such as:

* a legal obligation to which we are subject.
* consistent with the applicable law.
* litigation, investigations, audit and compliance practices, or to protect against legal claims.

Data disclosed to PayPal is subject to data retention periods as set out in the PayPal Privacy Statement.

How we use cookies and similar technologies

Like most other online services, PayPal Honey uses cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, and other markers (we'll just call them “cookies”) to collect some of the data discussed in this Privacy Statement. These help us operate our products, analyze engagement and usage, and provide a relevant and personalized shopping experience. See below to learn how you can manage your cookie preferences.  
  
Some cookies can be temporary (“session cookies” like those used for navigating your browser) and disappear once you close it. Others last longer (“persistent cookies,” like when you ask a site to remember your login) and are saved to your computer until you delete them.  
  
Our uses of cookies and similar technologies fall into the following general categories:

* **Essential**: We may use cookies, web beacons, or other similar technologies that are necessary to the operation of our sites, services, applications, and tools. This includes technologies that allow you access to our sites, services, applications, and tools; that are required to identify irregular site behavior, prevent fraudulent activity and improve security; or that allow you to make use of our functions such as shopping-carts, saved search, or similar functions;
* **Performance**: We may use cookies, web beacons, or other similar technologies to assess the performance of our websites, applications, services, and tools, including as part of our analytic practices to help us understand how our visitors use our websites, determine if you have interacted with our messaging, determine whether you have viewed an item or link, or to improve our website content, applications, services, or tools;
* **Functionality**: We may use cookies, web beacons, or other similar technologies that allow us to offer you enhanced functionality when accessing or using our sites, services, applications, or tools. This may include identifying you when you sign into our sites or keeping track of your specified preferences, interests, or past items viewed so that we may enhance the presentation of content on our sites;
* **Marketing**: We may use first-party or third-party cookies and web beacons to deliver content, including ads relevant to your interests, on our sites or on third party sites. This includes using technologies to understand the usefulness to you of the advertisements and content that have been delivered to you, such as whether you have clicked on an advertisement.

Any personal information that we collect and store through use of these technologies for categories other than “Essential” are based on your settings, managed through a conspicuous disclosure on our Website. You can change your preferences in your account settings at any time. If you want to disable cookies entirely, your browser or mobile device might have an option to do that. For more information, including instructions on disabling cookies, please visit: [https://allaboutcookies.org/](https://allaboutcookies.org/)

Your choices for managing your data

We've made it easy to opt out of PayPal Honey's products at any time.  
  
You can always adjust your personal settings regarding what information you share and how PayPal Honey communicates with you by going to your account page and clicking on the “personalize” or “emails” headings. Please note that limiting the information you offer to provide may impact PayPal Honey's ability to provide certain deals and products to you.  
  
If you want to stop using PayPal Honey, we have instructions on how to uninstall the Extension on our [Website](https://help.joinhoney.com/article/26-how-do-i-uninstall-honey) and if you have any issues you can contact our support team for assistance by sending an email to [yourfriends@joinhoney.com](mailto:yourfriends@joinhoney.com).  
  
You can also uninstall the PayPal Honey Mobile App in the same way you would uninstall other mobile apps from your mobile device.  
  
If you would like to delete your profile or personal information, you can always ask us by emailing [privacy@joinhoney.com](mailto:privacy@joinhoney.com). We will delete any personal information we have, although the following exceptions apply: (1) we may still store your personal information if we need it to meet our legal or compliance obligations and/or to defend against legal claims; and (2) we may also continue to store your personal data in an aggregated and anonymized format that doesn't identify you and can't be attributed to you, even after you've deleted your profile.

Learn More

Notice of Financial Incentive

If you are a California resident, you have a right to receive this Notice of Financial Incentive.  
  
Our rewards program, sometimes referred to as Honey Gold or PayPal Rewards, is offered with PayPal (together, “Rewards”) and provides you with the ability to earn points on eligible purchases, eligible PayPal transactions, or completing other actions, such as referring a friend.  
  
The Rewards can be earned through our Website, the PayPal Honey app, or through checkout and can be redeemed for gift cards, PayPal transaction discounts or cash back with a valid PayPal balance account. You can earn Rewards on purchases from eligible merchants, eligible PayPal transactions or other activity. The Rewards are subject to these [PayPal Rewards Program Agreement](https://www.paypal.com/us/legalhub/pp-rewards-program-tnc). Additional terms and exclusions may apply and are presented at the time the Reward is offered or saved.  
  
To manage Rewards the following Personal information is collected:

* Identifiers, such as name and email and account location
* Shopping and Usage Information, such as shopping history, transaction value and returns
* Preferred merchants or categories
* Internet and Network activity such as IP address
* Inferences drawn from one or more of the above, including a consumer's shopping history, that reflects a consumer's shopping preferences.

You opt into Rewards by registering for the Honey Services. You have the right to opt-out of the Rewards program by contacting customer support at [privacy@joinhoney.com](mailto:privacy@joinhoney.com), or you may uninstall or delete your account at any time  
  
To form the basis for the Rewards offered, PayPal Honey made the following good faith estimate of the value of the consumers' data based on the rewards granted by the business divided by the number of active participants over the past 12 months. We estimate the value of users’ personal information to be $15 per user.

Minors

We created PayPal Honey for the exclusive use of adults (18 and older). We don't knowingly collect or solicit personal information from children. If you are a child under 18, please do not attempt to use or register for PayPal Honey's products or send any personal information to us.

Learn More

How to contact us

If you have any questions about our privacy policies and practice, please contact our Privacy Officer at [privacy@joinhoney.com](mailto:privacy@joinhoney.com).  
  
Or you can write us a letter (fancy!) at:  
  
**PayPal Honey  
Attn: Privacy  
963 E. 4th Street  
Los Angeles, CA 90013**

About, Legal & More

### Company

### Product

### Legal

[Privacy](https://www.joinhoney.com/privacy)[Copyright](https://www.joinhoney.com/copyright)[Patents](https://www.joinhoney.com/patents)[Terms](https://www.joinhoney.com/terms)[Ad Disclosure](https://help.joinhoney.com/article/30-how-does-honey-make-money)[E-Communication](https://www.joinhoney.com/ecomms-policy)[Accessibility](https://www.joinhoney.com/accessibility)Cookies

### Follow Us

### Get the App

Google Play and the Google Play logo are trademarks of Google Inc.  
Apple and the Apple logo are trademarks of Apple Inc., registered in the U.S. and other countries. App Store is a service mark of Apple Inc., registered in the U.S. and other countries.

© 2024 PayPal, Inc.

Honey is now part of the PayPal family. Learn more  [here](https://help.joinhoney.com/article/302-what-does-honey-joining-paypal-mean-for-members).

United States

English
